The regular meeting of the Obama Special Utility Authority Board for December 6, 2021.
And we're going to have the implication by the pastor of the United Baptist Church, Mr. Mark Nichols.
Well, it's great. Emily Father will give you praise as his appropriate.
And with thank you for the love show us.
The blessings will show us primarily through your son Jesus Christ, but so many other woman blessings are good blessings that you're good to give.
And then with Father, in view of that, we're pray for these leaders, pray that the blessedness that they've endured, that our community hasn't endured.
We've inspired them to the greatest wisdom, which you've given the greatest wisdom, to lead as he would desire.
Because when we lead, in what it places you, if you only, we will always be blessed.
So, probably give them wisdom, give them the oldest words made it.
And just increase their ability to lead in a way that blesses them, blesses this community.
And it's a testimony to you, and we'll just pray for you in Jesus' name.
Amen.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America.
And to the Republic, for which it stands, one nation, another nation, another nation.
And it is the liberty and justice of our all.
And I was doing it.
Thank you.
Our forefork incentive, our student.
So, our forepublic input, our scheduled personal appearances.
Five, consent agenda.
Staff recommends we approve item six and seven.
So far.
Thank you.
Davis.
Sunder.
Hi.
Temple.
Eight, action on 22, meeting schedule.
We'll make a motion to approve.
Parker.
Five.
Sunder.
Davis.
Hi.
Nine.
Next time.
Letter of engagement.
We'll dance financial services to perform with 2022.
electric war, wastewater and solid waste rate study and non-rate study, or a fee study, and
this is the only table from last meeting.
So, Mr. Mayor, if I may, I've had some conversations with a couple of council members
to get for the direction on this, and one of the things I would recommend tonight is that
rather than tabling this so that it shows up on the next, there are still some items that
we want to talk through and possibly present to the council as a whole, and I think doing
that at a work session would make more sense.
So it probably would be sometime in mid to late January that we would want to put this
on the next work schedule in January.
So rather than tabling it, I would say that tonight, maybe we just take no action on this,
that way it removes it from the agenda, and then we can work with the council to get it on
the appropriate agenda in January.
I'll make the motion that we take no action.
Second.
Double.
High.
Sunder.
Davis.
High.
Team, the interaction item or any other new business has risen since the, posting on this agenda.
11.
Trustee your committee announcements.
12 adjournment.
So move.
Second.
Double.
Five.